Yes.
Girl named Marry called
on the pay-phone.
Said she's set her parents
and you're invited to dinner.
Oh, yeah?
Thank you very much.
You're late, Henry.
I didn't know if you wanted me
to come or not. Where have you been?
You never come
around anymore.
Dinner's almost ready.
Come on in.
Hello there.
Hello.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
Sit down.
It's Henry. isn't it?
Yes.
Marry tells me you're a very
nice fellow. What do you do?
I-I am on vacation.
What did you do?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I work in the Lapell's factory.
I am a printer.
Henry is very clever in printing.
Yes, he sounds very clever.
I thought I heard a stranger.
We've got chicken tonight. Strangest
damn things, they're man-made.
Little damn things,
smaller than my fist.
But they're new.
I'm Bill.
- Hello, I'm Henry.
- Henry is at Lapell's factory.
Print is your business, ha?
Plumbing is mine.
30 years. I've seen has never had changed
for patching to the hell how it is now!
I put every damn pipe
in this neighborhood.
- Dad!
- Bill!
Pipes ain't growing alone. I make sure
they don't. Look at my knees.
- Look at my knees!
- Bill!
- Are you hungry?
The girls had heard this before...
but 14 years ago, I had
an operation on my arm here.
Doctors said I won't be able to use it.
But what the hell do they know, I said.
And I rubbed it for a half hour every day
and I've got those... I could move it a little.
And I got... so I could turn a faucet
and pretty soon I had my arm back again.
Now I can't feel a damn
thing in it. All numb...
I'm afraid to cut it, you know.
Mary usually does the carving but
maybe tonight you'll do it, Henry.
All right with you?
Of course.
I'd be happy to.
I just... just cut them up
like regular chickens?
Sure, just cut them up
like regular chickens.
It'll be all right.
Excuse me.
Well, Henry, what do you know?
I don't know much of anything.
Henry, may I speak
to you a minute?
Over here.
Did you and Mary
have sexual intercourse?
- Why?
- Did you?
- Why are you asking me this question?
- I have a very good reason.
But now I want you to tell me.
I-I'm very... I love Mary.
Henry, I asked you if you
and Mary had sexual intercourse.
- I-I don't think it's any of your business.
- Henry!
Sorry.
You're in very bad trouble
if you won't cooperate.
Well... I...
- Mary!
- Mother!
- Answer me!
- I'm too nervous.
- There's a baby. It's at the hospital.
- Mom!
- And you're the father.
- It isn't possible...
- It's still unsure it is a baby.
- It's premature, but there's a baby.
After the two of you are married which should
be very soon, you can pick the baby up.
Mom, he's got
his nose bleeding.
I'll get ice.
Will you mind, Henry,
you and I getting married?
No!
This dinner is getting cold.
Is there any mail?
No.
Shut up!
I can't stand it.
I'm going home.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't even sleep. I'm loosing my mind.
You're on vacation, now.
You can take care of it for a night.
Will you come back tomorrow?
All I need is a decency of that sleep.
Why don't you just stay home?
I'll do what I wanna do.
And you better take real good
care of things while I'm gone.
Oh, you are sick...
Move over.
Move over!
I locked myself
out of my apartment.
And it's so late.
Where's your wife?
She must've gone
back to her parents, again.
I'm not sure.
Can I spend a night here?
In heaven everything is fine
You've got your good things
and I've got mine
In heaven everything is fine
You've got your good things
and you've got mine
In heaven...
...everything is fine
Ok, Paul!
Hi ya sonny,
what've you got there?
Counter, Paul!
It's ok.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player